"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
Master, are you okay?
Are you still alive?
master
I asked you if anything happened?
Master? Hello!
Well I'm fine
Oh my god
Oops
Damn, the car was a total wreck.
Oops, this is really going crazy
Where is my mobile phone?
(He Zhen)
Someone named Ha Zhen is calling you.
give me
Oops, hello?
Hello hubby
There was an accident here
Who are you?
He was helping me drive just now
Your husband is my chauffeur
Wife, it’s me
Husband
(Emergency Room)
Won't you go up?
Go up
- Then why don't you get off the car?
- I'll be up right away
Hurry up
Why haven't you come back yet?
What are you doing standing there? Go to sleep
Dad?
What's wrong?
Why did you go to be a contemporary driver?
Just do whatever you want. What's wrong? Any questions?
I like driving
Is it because of me?
Stop talking nonsense
Oops son
You have grown so big
When did you grow so tall?
Your mother is back
I'm so sorry that so many things happened so early in the morning.
You must not have had much sleep at all, right?
go to sleep
Suqian, go back to your room
Wife, let’s go get some sleep
Let's go
Where to go?
Go to psychiatry
Oops
You heard what the emergency doctor said.
Let's go there and listen to what they have to say.
The inspection results are all normal
Doctors are just talking nonsense...
You still don't trust the doctor? Okay, I understand.
Suqian, close the door
Then do you listen to me?
There are too many things I can't figure out now
I don't want to keep guessing all day long at home
this feels so bad
So don't listen to the doctor, listen to me
Go to a psychiatrist
- I'm not going
- go
If I say I'm fine, I'll be fine
(Go straight for 8 kilometers)
Hello?
Bastard, don't you have any idea?
Do you really think you are a big shot?
Megalomaniac
What to look at?
Look ahead
sorry
Shut up, asshole!
Don't pretend to be working
Get down to business. Who do you think you are?
Master, I told you to look at the front
Re-routing in progress
Hang up, bastard!
Are you sure you want to go here? This place...
This is the store I bought from
Sir, why are we going here?
In the end, you carried us on our backs for the rest of our lives.
A debt that I can't even repay.
You must have bought life insurance, right?
That's worse than
Wouldn't it be better just like this?
What do you think?
Dad, it’s time to have breakfast
Dad?
Dad!
Mom! Dad, he...
Dad, are you okay?
- I can't breathe.
- What's wrong?
- Husband
- I gasp...
What's going on?
- Husband
- Call an ambulance via mobile phone
- I can't breathe.
- Are you out of breath?
I think I need to go to the hospital
- Good Soo-gyeom!
- Where is my mobile phone?
- Go to the hospital now
- OK
- No
- Help him up
Let's send him there
Get up
Oh my god, look at all this sweat.
- Mom, wait a minute.
- OK
hey wife
I don't feel the need to go
What?
I'm feeling better now. Let's go back.
You have to go to work. It's time for you to go to class, right?
What?
I'm fine. Let's go up. Hurry.
Why are you like this? I told you I'm fine
Nothing happens to me
Nothing happened?
Yes, I just need to have a good sleep
Just relieve the pressure and you'll be fine
let's go up
Wake up, Kim Nak-soo!
Do you think this is normal?
Is this something a sane person would do?
Are you crazy?
Don't you think about your family at all?
You almost died!
you have to see a psychiatrist
A sane person would never do this
Let's go
Hurry up
OK I'll go
- OK
- Get on the bus
No, you don't have to go. Just go with your mother.
Go to class
Why are there so many people?
(The parking space is full, please wait in line)
Come on come on
(Yijiang General Hospital)
Let's get back to the car
What's wrong?
Look how serious you have become
How are you holding on during this time...
Go somewhere else. I'm fine.
Don't go to a general hospital. Go to a clinic. There are fewer people.
Why is the clinic closed again today?
Really
Come to the second floor when you have time
let's talk
Oops
Wait, in that case...
(Wangzhen Shopping Center)
(Start navigation)
let's go here
Do you know this place?
Episode 10: Patient No. 102
Let's go first.
(Huiyin Psychiatric Clinic)
Sorry, when will the doctor come?
I'm not sure. No one has made an appointment today.
He is probably enjoying his lunch slowly.
Please fill out the consultation form first
Something doesn't seem right about this place.
Just watch it here
(panic disorder symptom list)
(...Experienced uneasiness or fear? No)
(The attack reaches its peak a few minutes after it begins)
Well this...
(no)
(...change behavior to avoid seizures No)
answer honestly
I'm very honest
No, not this either
I'm back
Have you gone to have a big meal? What took you so long?
Shangyang snack bar closed down
Really?
So I ran all the way...
Huh?
You're here. It's on the first floor...
Okay let's go in
Doctor, please show me
Sir, bring the consultation form
please give it to me
(treatment room)
- Questionnaire
- OK
Go in
(Diagnosis and treatment areas: anxiety and panic disorder)
Would you like a cup of tea?
No thanks
Okay, please sit down for a while.
I'll leave in ten minutes
So Madam doesn’t know yet
What do you know?
What happened when you bought the shop on the first floor?
I know what to do
You have to confess to her quickly and let's discuss countermeasures together.
then take medicine
What medicine?
Of course it's medicine for panic disorder.
I'll prescribe two kinds for you. One is anti-anxiety medicine.
Take if you have a panic attack or have trouble breathing
-Another one is an antidepressant...
- Hello
You didn't even look at the consultation form
They didn't check me either.
How can you say I have panic disorder?
What a liar
I have confirmed your symptoms with my own eyes
When?
good
What? What does it mean?
Please come and take a look
What's wrong?
Optimistic
You walked over there that day
Then I felt it was getting harder and harder to breathe
You covered your chest and collapsed to the ground in front of this building.
Mr. Kim Nak-soo
I helped you that day
- Are you okay?
- Sorry
I am a doctor. Please give way.
sir look at me
Breathe here
take a deep breath
continue
Yes, I'm in front of Wangzhen Shopping Center
someone fell
There were no patients that day
I just kept looking out the window and happened to see
I just did my duty
So don't thank me
(Graduation certificate, professional qualification certificate)
I was admitted second
Graduated first
(Graduation Certificate Psychiatry)
I didn't ask
Anyway
As a psychiatrist, my diagnosis is
you have panic disorder
Oops
ok
Let’s call it “disease”
Cold, enteritis, muscle pain
And panic disorder, they are all diseases.
As long as I change my mentality
Be optimistic and live in a temple
Wouldn't it be nice to exercise?
No, this is not a disease that can be cured by willpower alone.
So what can I do to get better?
Let's take our time. Let's have a cup of tea first.
So can tea cure panic disorder?
No. That kind of tea does not exist.
Then I won’t drink
ok
drug treatment
Cognitive behavioral therapy and breathing exercises
The treatment of panic disorder goes like this step by step...
I don't have time to do this now
you know
I still have to take care of that damn store.
I don't have time to do this
- How did you take care of it?
- I have to clean every day
It’s so convenient to rent.
Do you really think it says "rent free for the first three months"?
Can it attract tenants?
So why did you come here to open a clinic?
How much is the monthly rent?
- I don’t pay monthly rent
- What?
I heard that a chain of coffee shops is planning to set up shop.
Are you excited?
- Right
-“Comparable to the business district of Gangnam Station”
“Three minutes walk to the subway station”
"The director will give you the best discount"
- Right
- When you said you wanted to buy it
He also asked you to discuss it with your family before coming.
Yes
He clicks on his tablet and calculator
It must be that posture that frightened you, right?
don't tell me...
Yes
I was also one of the first people to buy a shop here
Damn it
Oops
let's go
Hurry up
Sorry, I have to pay
Bring your medicine too
- OK
(Wangzhen Shopping Center)
Isn't this the clinic you insisted on coming to?
What's wrong?
Listen, wife
The doctor must at least be smarter than me, right?
- Right
- That way I can feel free to let him see me.
What then?
I think he's as stupid as me
I can't trust that guy
What on earth did you two talk about?
Boss!
- Boss!
- Oh, let's go
- Is she calling you? She...
- Where are you going?
Why don't you answer my call?
Did you admit the wrong person?
I finally waited for a phone call
He said he would come over tomorrow to have a look
- That...
- What do you say?
Just...
I remembered
I resigned from ACT
She is the boss of the company I worked with before
- She must not know that I have resigned.
- What are you talking about?
Someone wants to see No. 102
No. 102?
Are you his wife?
You must be worried, right?
You have to be nice to your wife. If something like this happens...
What?
I understand
I'll contact you tomorrow
The first three months are rent-free, right?
Yes
(Recruitment: 3 million won per month)
(The first three months are rent-free!
Catering, Coffee, Unmanned Stores (Preferred)
Did you buy this?
How much?
billion
fifty million
Wait
Where did that money come from?
I took out a loan of 550 million
What else?
Another 500 million...
It's retirement pay
severance pay...
This is our one billion and fifty million won store
I will try my best. I'm sorry.
Kim Nak Soo
I wanted to tell you, but I never had the chance
Kim Nak Soo!
- Kim Nak-soo
- Sorry
Please Kim Nak Soo
Kim Nak Soo
Kim Nak Soo!
sorry
Accept the reality and confess to your family
That's it
well done
(3208333 won)
give me one
Why are you doing this?
Ever since I got pregnant with Soo-gyeom, I haven’t had a smoking habit in 20 years.
But now I want to smoke like crazy
Give me one quickly
Sorry, please don't do this
What about stocks?
i sold
Have you sold both US and Korean stocks?
Where did that money go?
(mom)
(No. 517, Dongcheon-daero, Sinpyeong-si, Gyeonggi-do
Wangzhen Shopping Center)
Go straight and then turn left. Hey Soo-gyeom.
This way
Dad, what is this place?
Soo Gyeom is here
Kim Soo-gyeom
Huh?
your company representative
I borrowed 30 million in your name?
Really?
Yes
So in order to pay off the debt
You use the money your father gave you to start a business?
Yes
- OK
- Where are you going?
Do you two consider me family?
Of course there is
But so much money comes and goes...
How could you not discuss it with me once?
What do you want me to do now?
I don't know
I really don't know anything anymore
You go...
Wife
Dad, what's going on?
How did things become like this?
What is this place?
We can't go home for the time being.
Lazy guy, where are you?
Traveling?
So your house is empty?
Your daughter didn't go with you
Hey, didn’t you say last time that the third floor was empty?
Can Suqian and I stay here tonight?
Has anyone rented it?
Wow, it looks like a geomantic treasure.
Your building is never empty
OK, have fun.
good
Hey
Let's go to the jjimjilbang
Go there to discuss countermeasures
Let's go
Hello
Are you blaming me for snitching on my mother?
So what else can I do?
She grilled me like a tax inspector
I have to confess
Get up, let's go
I really don't understand you
What does it mean?
you really are
Is it an investment made for the sake of my mother and me?
Ouch
Do you want to show off to others?
"Even if you are kicked out of the company
I’m still doing fine.”
You want to prove yourself
Right? Dad
That's enough. Stop talking.
You boy
That's what you said when you asked me to repeat the reading.
You say it's all for my own good, but in the end...
You are just coveting
It’s just the title “Father of Seoul National University Students”
Isn't it?
You bastard
What does the family want?
What are you worried about...
You never understood and you never cared
Whether it's Seoul National University or this store...
None of this is what we want, Dad.
You worry: “I won’t die, right?
What should I do if it happens again next time?”
So you will make small changes to your body
have become extremely sensitive
Even if the heartbeat is just a little faster
Or breathing a little bit faster
You will all think...
Madam, this location is around the corner.
It can not only attract the flow of customers here,
And it can attract customers over there.
Take your time and watch
This shop has been vacant since I bought it, right?
Yes but...
Someone who can truly see its value
Not here yet
Yes
Thank you. I've finished reading.
OK, walk slowly and look forward to your wise decision.
Remember to contact us
Please wait here for a moment, don't leave yet
Did I say the wrong thing in front of your wife?
It's okay It's okay
It's only been a few days and you're already so haggard
Wipe the shit out of your eyes
Shave your beard too
Okay, please...
Good
- Really
- Remember to contact me
OK I will
Madam, don't just leave like that
I'll show you other places
Oops
Oh my god
Huh?
What are you doing?
Oops
Damn it
Are you sleeping here again?
What...
No more water
God, this building is really hopeless.
Sorry, Dr. Luo
I was so rude yesterday
Dr. Luo
Can you help me?
My eyes hurt so much
Dr. Luo
(natural mineral water)
So cool
Something bad almost happened
Thanks to you, I can wash my hair. Thank you.
After confessing to my wife
Feeling better?
How do you know?
I didn't mean to eavesdrop
There was always a sound outside, so I heard it
What kind of terrible hobby do you have?
do you remember
When was the first panic attack?
You might get into a serious accident
Panic disorder itself is not fatal
But
If in an emergency
What about sudden panic attacks?
Damn it
I'm telling you to scold him!
scold him!
Hello!
(Construction ahead, slow down)
Your whole life will collapse in an instant
that
My wife and I don't talk much about work.
Not to mention my son and...
Oops
Sitting face to face with a complete stranger
Talking about my own affairs and doing consultation...
I really can't do it
If it really doesn't work...
Then we
Change the place?
(Dr. Luo Dalong)
(Huiyin Psychiatric Clinic)
Aren't you coming back?
I am seeing a doctor
What then?
Anyway...
He and I joined the company at the same time
That guy has been a class principal all his life
then the company
Suddenly asked him to go to Ulleungdo
a few days later
He's in the company's underground parking lot
Lighted charcoal in his car
So that's it
From then on, whenever something happened at work,
I feel like it's hard to breathe
My chest feels like it's being strangled tightly
That's it
I understand
How big companies do things
It's really frustrating, you know?
The boss keeps putting pressure
The subordinates tried their best to climb up again
Oh my god
You probably don’t understand this feeling, right?
Minister Kim
I used to work at a university hospital
So what?
Factions, sides, workplace politics
It's the same over there too
Yes, I saw it on TV
Is the situation so bad where you are?
Really?
Don't talk about me anyway...
Tell me
Why did you resign?
Huh?
Could it be that your trusted senior betrayed you?
Really?
enough
Tell me about you
I really put my seniors
Treat him like a real brother, even closer than my real brother
For 25 years...
Hear you say that
I think store fraud was just the final trigger.
While still working in the company
The situation has seriously deteriorated
I'm talking about your mental state.
for koreans
The most stressful place is the workplace
Competing all the way from elementary school, middle school, and college entrance examination
Competing genes in our body
Full bloom in the workplace
I don't feel pressured by competition.
Yes, indeed some people would say that.
No, I mean it
I have felt that competition is part of life since I was a child
I compete with my brother at home
What do you compete with your brother for?
Results
Is your brother studying well?
Come on, he's always been number one.
He is also always the class president and student council president, which is quite impressive.
As the eldest son, he is naturally more favored
Studying is so good
My brother must always take priority at home, right?
My parents also secretly encourage this competition.
"To be recognized like your brother
You also have to show some results."
What about your brother later?
Went to a better university than you?
No
He repeated his studies for three years
Finally, I went to a private university abroad.
My job is better than his too
That means you win
At that time
How do you feel?
That's it for today
Is this the last one?
Yes
There's a lot left
Sorry, I will find another place to store it as soon as possible.
What are those at the back? Did you draw them?
My current roommate is an art student
I just paint casually as a hobby
Can I have a look?
Of course
wow
Which paintings did you paint?
This one and...the ones here are all painted by me.
Hannah, this is more than just a hobby.
- Really?
- Yeah
There's something special about your paintings...
Something special?
Is there any?
Hannah, do you want these pictures?
On our hoodies?
- This?
- Right
No, it's so embarrassing
These are not yet ready to be sold.
No
Please, it's much better than this
That's true
(Love is here)
Have you ever thought about studying art?
I've thought about it. I like painting very much.
I have also applied to several design schools
How many have been admitted?
That's it
What happened next?
My dad wants me to repeat my studies for another year
I ended up going to Michigan Tech
That's not where I should be at all
you know
Why are parents like this?
The problem is their approach
I think that is also a kind of love
Because they probably grew up that way too
So I can only express it in that way.
Okay, I want three sample clothes first.
Okay, I'll see you then. Thank you.
Said let's pick it up next week
Your mobility is so strong
I'm leaving
Where are you going to sleep tonight?
I plan to go to the jjimjilbang
Internet cafes are not very...
Do you want to sleep here?
What?
Damn it
- boss
- What's wrong? Are you in a hurry?
No, no rush
someone is looking for you
Oops
(Complete car maintenance)
Who?
That one
- You go to work first
- It's the boss
Haojun
Hey!
Kim Nak-soo, Managing Director
Is there anything less sweet?
Is the car owner here for a regular inspection?
(maintenance record)
I checked the maintenance records
Just need to replace the tires
good
Want to try it?
No more
You can learn how to change a tire in ten minutes
Just like building with Lego
Forget it. Why bother?
Is this job profitable?
Sometimes it's not bad
Sometimes I earn less than them
Yongji, it's getting late. Let's call it a day.
good boss
good
Let's go after dinner, right?
I'm not hungry
Then what are you here for?
I see there seems to be a sofa over there
- What?
- Can I sleep here for one night?
- Did you quarrel with your siblings?
- OK or not?
are you asleep?
What? Nothing. What happened?
thank you
Thank you for what?
I have always been envious
My roommate can hold a solo exhibition
But now it’s you who made me paint
appeared for the first time
thank you really
can i...
Come closer?
What?
I have something to say
How close do you want to get?
I want to muster up some courage
you know...
If...
without your words
I can't do anything
you...
let me...
want to be a better person
i am very grateful to you
I like it very much
so i hope we
Can we keep going like this?
Then you have to go to bed early
good night
good
You too
(Speedmate Auto Repair
Tire service (entrust with confidence)
You can sleep at my house
Oops, I don't want to go
Have you cheated?
please
Yeah, you can't do such a thing
Where is Soo Gyeom?
I heard he repeated his studies
He went to Yanxi University
Really? Wow
He is the first one in our family to be admitted to three prestigious universities.
Hey, give him a call?
Let me talk to him. I haven't talked to him in a long time.
Forget it
You also have some time
Haven’t you seen my Xiaojun and Ruiren?
look
The children have grown so big
Say something, brat
Did you later become a senior executive?
I resigned
What?
You've worked there long enough
I was fired
Demoted to factory
He always disobeyed orders there too
So he was kicked out
heard this
How do you feel?
What do you mean?
I heard that I was not promoted to a senior executive in the end.
He was fired by the company
How do you feel?
I was just wondering how much severance pay you got
I took 500 million won
It all ended up being a stupid thing.
How do you feel? How do you feel when you hear this?
What on earth do you want to say?
You didn't get admitted to Seoul National University
I'm very happy
International Monetary Fund Crisis
You were laid off from your company
And when you lose everything in business
To be honest, I'm really happy
How is it? Have you changed your mind now?
I don't know
When I was a child, my mother once bought bananas.
Banana?
Bananas were very valuable back then
One string is about 100,000 won in today’s currency.
Mom gave me two
I gave you three
But when I got home from school, there was only one left on the table.
I'll go find you
I asked you why there is only one left on the table.
You don't remember?
What did I say?
You say you don't know
I'll go to your room and dig through the trash can
Turn out the banana peel
I'll show it to you and yell at you
Asking why you ate mine
Do you know what you did then?
you slapped me
I cried to find my mother
But she said
“What’s wrong with your brother eating one more?
What’s the big deal?”
I said you hit me and she just ignored me.
Hey
This is how I exist at home
When I was in third grade, it was my first time
Become the deputy squad leader and go home happily
Do you remember what you said?
Don't remember
You don't remember?
Damn it, I told you I don’t remember!
Hey, so you...
Don't remember anything
I am the only one who remembers
I'll sleep first
Didn’t the people who came to see the house yesterday also want to rent?
"Free rent for the first three months" has no effect
Then help me add short-term rentals to the list.
This might be best
Take your time and watch
OK thank you
I almost forgot, ma'am.
Please advise the boss not to sleep here as much as possible
What?
He looks so desperate that way
In the eyes of potential tenants
This is a big minus
Wait, he slept here?
Oh, you don't know
Ah, take your time and take a look
What is that?
Oops
(Super urgent sale)
(Super urgent sale, original price 500 million, current price 380 million)
(for rent)
(Recruitment: 3 million won per month)
Nak Soo, Kim Nak Soo
Oops
come in
The house has been bought, what else are you nagging about?
Sit down and listen to me, Suqian, you sit down too
- Ouch
- Sit quickly
Come and listen
From the entrance to the toilet
Go to Soo-gyeom's room again
Used me from ordinary staff to agent
A full ten years' salary
Next
The kitchen, the function room, and this bedroom
It cost me five years’ salary as a section chief
Finally, when I grow up these five years
I worked my ass off and used up all my savings.
It took a lot of effort to buy this living room and balcony
You're always complaining that you've had enough of moving.
That's why I bought this house
But don't you two forget
this apartment
What condensed my 51 years
painstaking effort
It's my trophy
Do you understand?
You are the best!
Dad, you are the best!
come on
You've worked hard too, wife
Thank you for your hard work!
This is our home!
let's have a drink
OK
What should we do?
This trophy cannot be used as food.
Hey you're up
I'm leaving
Good
thank you for taking me in
Yeah
- good morning
You guys are lazy. Why didn't you come earlier?
What's wrong? We arrived five minutes early
- Hello
Ask him, go ahead
No, just ask
Sorry, are you the boss's brother?
- Ah!
- give it to me
They look nothing alike
Look at their faces. It's obvious.
You have so much money that you have nowhere to spend it, right?
Brat, hurry up and change your clothes.
Yes
The boss often mentions you
What did he say?
Say that you are proud to hold a very high position in ACT...
- Hello!
- Okay, let's go
- Come on, buy me a cup of coffee.
- What?
This guy talks too much
Let's go
I put something on my desk in the office
Remember to take it
I ate it. Sorry.
What would happen if my brother apologized at that time?
If I become the deputy squad leader
How about he say "congratulations"?
Will I be different?
- Why is it different?
- Maybe I won't feel it
Everyone in the world is my competitor
There would be no such strong jealousy and sense of superiority
Will this happen?
Oh no one would know this
Unless we can go to a parallel universe
Besides, maybe it’s that competitive spirit
That’s why you’ve been able to hold on all the way until now
Feed the whole family
You're right, that's right
Alternatively, this could also be
In order to prove that your sword is still young
The reason why I made that high-risk investment
Suddenly lost my appetite
How many children do you have?
i have a son
Then you must have thought of yourself as a child
What I didn’t get from my parents
love and encouragement
You're all focused on your son, right?
- Well...
- Will express his love frequently
I dare not say anything else, but in terms of his education
I always give him the best
Send him to the best cram school
I also found him a tutor
I've done everything I can do
Do you know what that sounds like to me?
“I took the bananas I didn’t eat when I was a kid
I bought them all for him.”
That's what it sounds like
But now
These bananas only cost 3,000 won per bunch.
Wife
Wife?
Very good
Let me take a look
What delicious food did you make today?
Do you want me to cook another pack?
No
If your mother got off work early
I got home at almost six o'clock
Want something to eat?
No, you can eat it, Dad
Where have you been living lately?
Internet cafe or my friend’s house
Good
Hello
Did you really not want to repeat your studies in the first place?
That's my own decision
Add some rice?
Don't
- Mom gets home at six o'clock...
- It won't be long
No dad
What's wrong?
What did I tell you?
Fortunately we didn't cook an extra pack of instant noodles
Just listen to dad and good things will happen. Do you hear me?
You still want to add rice? I stopped you.
You boy
Did she go in?
be careful
Did she go up?
she's gone
- Do you want to continue driving?
- Right
- What? Feel embarrassed?
- No
Why should I feel ashamed when you go to work?
I'm just worried that something will happen to you again
No way, boy
Last time something happened because of a crazy customer.
I'll be careful, don't worry
Go in
Actually...
Do you want to work together?
Why do you want to come together?
What is "why"
I have a debt of thirty million to repay.
Oops
Can you go to Pyeongtaek so late?
How are you going to come back?
It's okay sir
your key
- Thank you for your hard work
- thank you
good
back
(Waiting for order)
Got an order!
Where to go?
Going to Suwon
(Contact customer)
Let's go
- to you
- thank you
Wait
your tip
- Thank you sir
- You're welcome
- Thank you for your hard work
- Soo Gyom!
Look! Got the tip
Why is it so delicious?
There are eggs in it
Eat slowly, dad. Be careful of food accumulation.
Aren't you tired?
Not tired, nothing
Dad is exhausted
And it's still cold
Dad, are you cold?
What if...
(Waiting for order)
- We have an order. Let's go.
- Got it
Quick let's go
Ouch my legs ouch
(Profits can be withdrawn)
We made 340,000 won, Dad
Is it because of the long journey?
After deducting 40,000 for gas, there is about 300,000 left.
- Right
- Oops
I take 160,000, you take 140,000
Why?
That hoodie of yours costs 10,000 won
So stingy
cut
How many pieces of this dress have been sold?
- Almost a hundred pieces
- One hundred pieces?
More than I thought
No more
You are better than me, son
My shop has been empty for three months
I can finally give you a pat on the head.
So do you plan to continue doing it?
I have to do it
Right
This is how business is done
Sometimes it goes well, sometimes it doesn't go well
The market trend is very subtle.
So you should listen to what others say more often.
Those restaurant ladies and taxi drivers?
You can read market trends from their words
What you missed is valuable consultation.
Okay, let's take a nap.
Must be exhausted
But dad is not tired
Really, even going home is all based on my own happiness.
OK
Oops
We are Soo-gyeom
(House photos open)
(Zhixiangjia upload photos)
(Publish property)
(Do you want to publish this property?)
(release)
(House listing completed)
"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
I told you not to sell the house
Would you like to give it a serious try?
Do you really think I can survive in that kind of environment?
Are you going to see the president?
Du Zhenyu betrayed me and took refuge with Special Agent Huang Taishan
It’s because I’m fed up with being treated like a transparent talent.
Hey Luo Zhu
Please help me one last time
It must be something you have to do.
Only you can do it
Kim Nak-soo Executive Director
Subtitle translation: Cheng Jiayue